Today, even after wandering from door to door with a box in the entire village, I could
not find ghee.  So ever since our
buffalo said, "Sir, I am pregnant,"
ghee and milk have all stopped and I am a
ghee-crazy person who even likes Maggi cooked in ghee.
What do you mean by desi ladka gum ki
hum and today I am craving to eat halwa.
Absolutely by adding ghee.  That's why my mother and I went out with a
box in the village
in search of ghee and with great difficulty I
found 1 kg of ghee.  Now if I want to make halwa, then
first I will have to make jaggery syrup.
But what is this, the surprise came before the good.
Oh my god, what have these Alpagunes people
sent for me, the crazy ghee man?  Such a lovely
note and ghee in such a cute jar.  Hey, I have
also sent a copper band for skin care.
Along with this, the packaging of this ghee moisturizer is also
exactly like a bronze plate.  New look,
new logo.  Wow man, it is very tough to make this at home.  It's
good that I found this.
It also helps in repairing the skin barrier.  It
also provides soft and nourished skin and keeps it moisturized for two whole days.
It is non-
greasy and very light weight which gets
absorbed easily into the skin.
Inspired by traditional skin care rituals, this cleanser gives a
cooling sensation.  So
I've tacked this Alpgnes Ghee Moisturizer
from perp.com on to you.  So while we were talking,
my hot
halwa made in ghee is also ready.  Which I have
decorated with dry fruits.  So now let
me just wrap this up and pack all this stuff away.
Radhe-Radhe.